No one is safe.
Texas Killing Fields is a drama, thriller, crime
film directed by Ami Canaan Mann.
In the Texas bayous, a local homicide detective teams up with a cop from
New York City to investigate a series of unsolved murders.
Mike Souder, played by Sam Worthington.
Brian Heigh, played by Jeffrey Dean Morgan.
Pam Stall, played by Jessica Chastain.
Little Ann Sliger, played by Chloë Grace Moretz.
Rule, played by Jason Clarke.
Gwen Heigh, played by Annabeth Gish.
Texas Killing Fields (also known as The Fields) is a 2011 American crime film directed by Ami Canaan Mann
and starring Sam Worthington, Jeffrey Dean Morgan, Jessica Chastain and Chloë Grace Moretz.
It competed in the 68th Venice International Film Festival.
The film's screenplay was loosely inspired by the history of killings along 30-plus miles of the Interstate 45
(I-45) corridor between Houston and Galveston, in and around an area known as "the Killing Fields".
The true events include the murders of women kidnapped from cities spread along the I-45 corridor and
dumped in many areas, including various bayous surrounding the oil fields of Texas City, Texas.
While in real life there have been several itinerant serial killers involved over
the years, the film focuses on specific local Texas City suspects.
The film explores themes of torture, series of
murders, multiple murder, woman director.
The tone is mind_bending and emotional and intense.